<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Hello, my name is Jonathan Robinson.</title>
    <link>https://jonrobinson2.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Hello, my name is Jonathan Robinson.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jonrobinson2.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I asked a biased sample of people what they think the electorate will look in 2016, here&#39;s what I learned.</title>
      <link>https://jonrobinson2.github.io/posts/I-Asked-A-Biased-Sample-Of-People-How-They-Think-The-Voting-Electorate-Will-Look-Like/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonrobinson2.github.io/posts/I-Asked-A-Biased-Sample-Of-People-How-They-Think-The-Voting-Electorate-Will-Look-Like/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;It all comes down to turnout&amp;rdquo; is a phrase uttered by countless analysts, pundits, and armchair elections quarterbacks alike. Over 4 days from September 30th to October 4th I surveyed the views of 400 non-random people a few questions about who they thought would vote in 2016 by pushing them to take a survey on the Survey Monkey platform. The goal here is not to ask a representative sample of individuals anything but hoping that the group of people interested in taking the survey have some insights into something that we won&amp;rsquo;t really have a great understanding of until voter files update with turnout records or at least the Census reports on voter turnout come out in the coming months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra Graphs</title>
      <link>https://jonrobinson2.github.io/posts/Extra-Graphs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonrobinson2.github.io/posts/Extra-Graphs/</guid>
      <description> I got more than a few questions about how this looks like for other candidates so I figure I would put up the full sets of graphs that come from this analysis here for both the full Republican field as well as the full Democratic field.
Interviewer vs. Non Interviewer Polls (Republican Field) Interviewer vs. Non Interviewer Polls (Democratic Field) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Polling Actually Understates Trump&#39;s Support Among Republicans</title>
      <link>https://jonrobinson2.github.io/posts/Public-Polling-May-Be-Understating-Trumps-Support/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonrobinson2.github.io/posts/Public-Polling-May-Be-Understating-Trumps-Support/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s the deal with Trump support? Like many a Jewish public opinion researcher, this past weekend I found myself sitting at a Rosh Hashannah dinner table talking with people about of all things, Donald Trump. Anticipating this, I dug a bit into &amp;lsquo;the Donald&amp;rdquo;s numbers in publicly available top-line polling data in an attempt to gain some semblance of a nugget to share with my dining companions.
What I found was fascinating and sheds a valuable light on Donald Trumps candidacy and public opinion on controversial people and issues in general.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>